Hula, Erich; Papers ger044
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Course and lecture notes, 4; 29 file folders
  - International Relations, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 11)
  - Intervention, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 12)
  - Jurisprudence, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 13)
  - Klemens von Klemperer, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 14)
  - League of Nations, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 15)
  - National Self-determination, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 16)
  - Socialist international law, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 17)
  - Soviet union, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 18)
  - Suez Canal, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 19)
  - U.N. Charter revisions, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 20)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Article 1, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 21)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Article 2, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 22)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 3-6, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 23)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 8-22, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 24)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 24-26, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 25)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 39-54, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 26)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 55-83, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 27)
  - U.N. Charter revisions - Articles 95-110, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous handwritten notes, Undated (Box 6 (4-Course and lecture notes), Folder 29)
- Note Cards and Loose Leaf Pages, 5; 106 half folders
  This series consists of a combination of 5" x 8" note cards and 6" x 9" loose leaf sheets with handwritten notes on various topics, as well as reading notes on books read by Hula.
  - America, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 1)
  - American history, 1643-1781 (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 2)
  - American history and government, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 3-4)
  - American regionalism, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 5)
  - Arbitration, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 6)
  - The Bricker Amendment, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 7)
  - Canada, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 8)
  - Crimes against peace, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 9-10)
  - Domestic jurisdiction, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 11)
  - Draft covenant, 1950 (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 12)
  - Equality of nations, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 13)
  - European Economic Community / NATO, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 14)
  - European Integration, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 15)
  - Federalism, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 16-17)
  - Federalist, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 18-19)
  - Freedom of Association, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 20)
  - Freedom of Information, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 21)
  - Fundamentals of Reconstruction, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 22)
  - Human Rights, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 23)
  - Human Rights / Crisis, Undated (Box 7 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 24-25)
  - Imperial Russia, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 1-4)
  - International Bill of Rights, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 5)
  - International Capitalism and Administration, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 6)
  - International Criminal Law, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 7)
  - International Law, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 8-12)
  - International Law & International Organizations, Undated (Box 8 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 13-17)
  - International Organizations, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 1-4)
  - International Relations, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 5-8)
  - Interpretation problems, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 9)
  - Jurisprudence, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 10-11)
  - Kelsen / Kelsen Festschrift, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 12-15)
  - Law of the Land, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 16)
  - Laws of War, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 17-18)
  - League of Nations, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 19)
  - Majority principle, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 20-21)
  - Minorities, Undated (Box 9 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 22)
  - National Self-determination, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 1)
  - Nationalism, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 2)
  - Pan-Americanism, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 3)
  - Parliamentary government, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 4)
  - Peace Treaties, 1947 (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 5)
  - Political Economics, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 6-7)
  - Post-war peace, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 8)
  - Sovereignty under attack, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 9-11)
  - Treaties, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 12-13)
  - Typology of federal law, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 14)
  - United Nations, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 15-22)
  - United Nations Reenvisioned, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 23-24)
  - Völkerrecht, Undated (Box 10 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 25)
  - Reading notes, Undated (Box 11 (5-Note Cards and Loose Leaf ), Folder 1-17)
- Individual Author Files, 6; 323 file folders
  This series consists primarily of reprints sent to Hula by other authors with some original typescripts and secondary materials. There is a large section on Hans Kelsen (33 folders) as well as a number of reprints and other materials on: Hans Aufricht, Arnold Brecht, Leo Gross, Otto Kirchheimer, Josef L. Kunz, Karl Loewenstein, Hans J. Morgenthau, Egon Schwelb and Kurt von Fritz.
  - Abel, Reuben, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 1)
  - Ago, Roberto, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 2)
  - Akzin, Benjamin, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 3)
  - Almond, Gabriel A., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 4)
  - Anderson, William, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 5)
  - Apel, Karl-Otto. "Causal Explanation, Motivational Explanation, and Hermeneutical Understanding", Undated; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 6)
  - Arbesmann, Rudolph, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 7)
  - Aronson, David, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 8)
  - Aronson, Moses J., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 9)
  - Ashcraft, Richard, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 10)
  - Aspaturian, Vernon V., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 11)
  - Aufricht, Hans, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12)
  - Berger, Peter, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 13)
  - Bernays, Edward L., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 14)
  - Bernstein, Richard J. "Nietzsche or Aristotle? (Reflections on MacIntyre's After Virtue), 1984; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 15)
  - Biermann, Benno, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 16)
  - Bloom, Alan D., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 17)
  - Bondy, Otto, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 18)
  - Borchard, Edwin M., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 19)
  - Brecht, Arnold. "Innere Landschaft. Lyrisches Vermächtnis", Undated; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 20)
  - Brecht, Arnold. "Studies in Legal Philosophy. Ed. William R. Andersen" (review), 1960 December; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 21)
  - Brecht, Arnold, Undated; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 22)
  - Brecht, Arnold. Articles, clippings about, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 23)
  - Briggs, Herbert W., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 24)
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 25)
  - Burin, Frederic S., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 26)
  - Campbell, Blair, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 27)
  - Chai, Winberg, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 28)
  - Christoph, James B., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 29)
  - Clark, Grenville. Articles about, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 30)
  - Claude, Inis L. Jr., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 31)
  - Cobban, Alfred, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 32)
  - Cole, Taylor, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 33)
  - Cook, Thomas I., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 34)
  - Cornides, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 35)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, Richard. Articles about, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 36)
  - Cropsey, Joseph, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 37)
  - Dean, Howard E., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 38)
  - De Grazia, Sebastian, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 39)
  - Diamond, Martin, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 40)
  - Domke, Martin, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 41)
  - Dowling, R. E., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 42)
  - Eagleton, Clyde, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 43)
  - Eckstein, Harry, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 44)
  - Einaudi, Manon Michels, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 45)
  - Engelmann, Frederick C., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 46)
  - Fairlie, John A., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 47)
  - Faulkner, Robert K., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 48)
  - Fetscher, Iring, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 49)
  - Field, G. Lowell, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 50)
  - Finer, S. E., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 51)
  - Fischer, Eric, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 52)
  - Fosdick, Dorothy, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 53)
  - Fraenkel, Ernst, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 54)
  - Frankel, Joseph, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 55)
  - Fried, John H. E., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 56)
  - Friedrich, Carl J., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 57)
  - Friesenhahn, Ernst. "Neuerliche Erwägungen zum politischen Eid", 1978; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 58)
  - Friesenhahn, Ernst, Undated; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 59)
  - Funke, Gerhard, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 60)
  - Gavre, Mark, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 61)
  - Ginsburgs, George, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 62)
  - Götz, Hans Herbert, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 63)
  - Goodhart, Arthur L., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 64)
  - Grabowsky, Adolf, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 65)
  - Grant, J. A. C., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 66)
  - Gross, Leo, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 67)
  - Gurian, Waldemar. "Der Vater des Bolschewismus und Faschismus? Georges Sorel", Undated; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 68)
  - Haberler, Gottfried. "Fritz Machlup: In memoriam", Undated; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 69)
  - Haberler, Gottfried, Undated; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 70)
  - Hägele, Michael P., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 71)
  - Hallowell, John H., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 72)
  - Hartmann, Paul, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 73)
  - Heidenheimer, Arnold J., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 74)
  - Helson, Harry, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 75)
  - Henle, Mary, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 76)
  - Hennis, Wilhelm. "Germany: The Lawmaker and the German University", 1977; Typescript (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 77)
  - Hennis, Wilhelm, Undated; Reprints (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 78)
  - Hentschel, Rolf, Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 79)
  - Hermens, Ferdinand A., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 80)
  - Hertz, Wilhelm G., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 81)
  - Herz, John H., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 82)
  - Hexner, Ervin P., Undated (Box 12 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 83)
  - Hoffmann, Ross, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 1)
  - Holsti, Ole R., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 2)
  - Horvath, Barna, Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 3)
  - Horvath, Barna. Reviews by, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 4)
  - Horvath, Barna. Articles about, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 5)
  - Houghton, Neal D., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 6)
  - Houn, Franklin W., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 7)
  - Hucker, Charles O., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 8)
  - Hula, Annemarie, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 9)
  - Huntington, Samuel P., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 10)
  - Jaffa, Harry V. "Abraham Lincoln and the American Creed", 1950; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 11)
  - Jaffa, Harry V., Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12)
  - Jenks, C. Wilfred, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 13)
  - Jessup, Philip C., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Alvin. Articles about, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 15)
  - Jonas, Hans. "Heidegger and Theology", Undated; Typescript, mimeo (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 16)
  - Jonas, Hans. "Jewish and Christian Elements in the Western Philosophical Tradition", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 17)
  - Jonas, Hans, Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 18)
  - Kann, Robert A., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 19)
  - Kariel, Henry S., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 20)
  - Kaufmann, Felix, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 21)
  - Kempner, Robert M. W., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 22)
  - Kendall, Willmore, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 23)
  - Kenney, Charles D., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 24)
  - Kennington, Richard, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 25)
  - Kirchheimer, Otto, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 26)
  - Kissinger, Henry, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 27)
  - Klein, Fritz, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 28)
  - Klein, Jacob. "On the Nature of Nature", 1969; Typescript, mimeo (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 29)
  - Kohn, Hans, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 30)
  - Kohn, Walter S. G., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 31)
  - Kolnai, Aurel, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 32)
  - Koyré, Alexandre, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 33)
  - Kunz, Josef L. Editorials from The American Journal of International Law, 1945-1952 (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 34)
  - Kunz, Josef L., 1941-1949; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 35)
  - Kunz, Josef L., 1950-1960; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 36)
  - Kunz, Josef L. Articles about, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 37)
  - Landynski, Jacob, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 38)
  - Larmore, Charles. "Political Neutrality: On Liberalism and the State", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 39)
  - Legaz y Lacambra, Luis, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 40)
  - Leibholz, Gerhard, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 41)
  - Lemarchand, René, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 42)
  - Levitan, David M., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 43)
  - Lewis, Ewart, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 44)
  - Lewy, Guenther, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 45)
  - Loewenberg, Gerhard, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 46)
  - Loewenstein, Karl, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 47)
  - Löwith, Karl, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 48)
  - Losonczy, Stephan, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 49)
  - Lowe, Adolph. "Conflicting Paradigms in Economics. A Self-Critique", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 50)
  - Lowe, Adolph. "Inflation and Social Distribution", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 51)
  - Lowe, Adolph, Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 52)
  - Lowenthal, David, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 53)
  - Luckmann, Benita. "Alfred Schutz and Aron Gurwitsch at the New School", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 54)
  - Luckmann, Benita. "New School Varianten der Rueckkehr aus Exil und Emigration", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 55)
  - Luckmann, Benita, Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 56)
  - Luckmann, Thomas, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 57)
  - Ludz, Peter Christian. "Thomas S. Kuhns Paradigmathese: Eine ideologiekritische Untersuchung", Undated; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 58)
  - Ludz, Peter C., Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 59)
  - Macdonald, R. St. J., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 60)
  - Macmahon, Arthur W., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 61)
  - Manner, George, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 62)
  - Mason, Alpheus Thomas, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 63)
  - Matthiesen, Ulf. "Im Schatten einer endlosen großen Zeit. Etappen der intellektuellen Biographie Albert Salomons", 1986; Typescript (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 64)
  - Mays, Wolfe, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 65)
  - McCloskey, Robert G., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 66)
  - McClosky, Herbert, Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 67)
  - McCoy, Charles N. R., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 68)
  - McKenna, Joseph C., Undated (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 69)
  - Merkl, Adolf.Die Lehre von der Rechtskraft, 1923 (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 70)
  - Merkl, Adolf, Undated; Reprints (Box 13 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 71)
  - Métall, Rudolf Aládar, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 1)
  - Meyer, Hans, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 2)
  - Mises, Ludwig von. "Epistemological Relativism in the Sciences of Human Action", 1959; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 3)
  - Mises, Ludwig von, Undated; Reprints (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 4)
  - Moór, Julius, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 5)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J. "Preface to a Political Theory of Foreign Aid", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 6)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J. "The Real Issue Between the United States and the Soviet Union", 1962; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 7)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1938-1949; Reprints (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 8)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1950-1954; Reprints (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 9)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1955-1959; Reprints (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 10)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1960-1964; Undated; Reprints (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 11)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1965-1977; Reprints, clippings (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 12)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J. Articles about, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 13)
  - Morris, Bernard, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 14)
  - Morstein-Marx, Fritz, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 15)
  - Moslar, Hermann, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 16)
  - Mosely, Philip E., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 17)
  - Neal, Fred Warner, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 18)
  - Nef, John Ulric, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 19)
  - Neisser, Hans P., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 20)
  - Nelson, Benjamin, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 21)
  - Nenning, Günther, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 22)
  - Neunreither, Karlheinz, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 23)
  - Nicolaysen, Gert, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 24)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold. "The Limits of Principle in International Politics: Necessity and the New Balance of Power", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 25)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold. "The Moral Question in International Relations", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 26)
  - Niebuhr, Reinhold. "The Ultimate Validity and the Ideological Distortions of Moral Concepts in International Politics", Undated; Typescript (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 27)
  - Odložilík, Otakar, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 28)
  - Oppenheim, Felix E., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 29)
  - Osgood, Robert E., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 30)
  - Padgett, L. Vincent, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 31)
  - Padover, Saul K., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 32)
  - Palmer, Norman D., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 33)
  - Pangle, Thomas L., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 34)
  - Pauli, Hertha. Articles about, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 35)
  - Pauli, Wolfgang. Articles about, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 36)
  - Peffer, Nathaniel, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 37)
  - Pekelis, Alexander H., Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 38)
  - Pennock, J. Roland, Undated (Box 14 (6-Individual Author Files), Folder 39)